<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Slots>
 <slot name="systems">
  <display>APU</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the ship's auxiliary power unit (APU). The APU provides power to the ship's battery, shield, and components.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="hull">
  <display>Hull</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the ship's hull. It provides the ship's armor – the last line of protection from hazards and the vacuum of space – as well as storage space for cargo.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="engines">
  <display>Engine</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the ship's engine. The engine propels and turns the ship. Engines require energy from the core system to function.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="bio_systems">
  <display>Bioship Heart</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the heart, the biological equivalent to an APU. The heart of an organism is responsible for allocating energy for the battery, shield, and other organs or components.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="bio_hull">
  <display>Bioship Shell</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the shell, the biological equivalent to a hull. The shell is the last line of defense for the organism, protecting critical organs from damage. It is also helps determine the organism's cargo space.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="bio_engines">
  <display>Bioship Fin</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the fin, the biological equivalent to an engine. The fins propels the organism thru space.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="bio_weapon">
  <display>Bioship Weapon</display>
  <description>In addition to standard weapons, this slot can be used for special organic weapons which can only be equipped to bioships. Organic weapons are generally similar to their synthetic counterparts, but more efficient, which is important to compensate for the reduced CPU capacity of the brain in comparison to synthetic constructs.</description>
 </slot>
 <slot name="fighter_bay">
  <display>Fighter Bay</display>
  <description>This slot can be used for fighter bays.</description>
 </slot>
</Slots>
