<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Slots>
 <slot name="systems">
  <display>Core System</display>
  <description>This slot is used for dedicated core system of the ship. Other subsystems rely on this system to manage them, and the bulk of the ship's power and shield generation also happens here.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="hull">
  <display>Hull</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the ship's hull. It represents the base layer of armour plating and protection from the vacuum of space, and also determines the ship's baseline mass and cargo capacity.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="engines">
  <display>Engine</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the ship's engine. The engine propels and turns the ship. Engines require energy from the core system to function.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="bio_systems">
  <display>Bioship Brain</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the brain, the biological equivalent to core systems. The brain of an organism is responsible for managing the function of the rest of the organism and allocating energy reserves for the battery and shield.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="bio_hull">
  <display>Bioship Shell</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the shell, the biological equivalent to a hull. The shell is the last line of defense for the organism, protecting critical organs from damage. It is also helps determine the organism's cargo space.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="bio_engines">
  <display>Bioship Fin</display>
  <description>This slot is used for the fin, the biological equivalent to an engine. The fins propels the organism thrû space.</description>
  <exclusive/>
  <required/>
 </slot>
 <slot name="bio_weapon">
  <display>Bioship Weapon</display>
  <description>In addition to standard weapons, this slot can be used for special organic weapons which can only be equipped to bioships. Organic weapons are generally similar to their synthetic counterparts, but more efficient, which is important to compensate for the reduced CPU capacity of the brain in comparison to synthetic constructs.</description>
 </slot>
 <slot name="fighter_bay">
  <display>Fighter Bay</display>
  <description>This slot can be used for fighter bays.</description>
 </slot>
</Slots>
